squadlocker.com 2017-06-25

# SquadLocker© Privacy Policy

## Information we collect

In order to provide you with access to the Site, we may gather and process some or all of the following information:

• Order Information: information that is collected or stored by or from users of the Site in connection with orders from the site, including request for customizations, etc.

• Reviews and Comments: information that is voluntarily provided by user of the site (such as reviews, suggestions, etc.).

• Registration Information: any information provided when voluntarily registering for use of the Site, including, but not limited to, username and password and email address.

• Customer Communications: any information that is reported to us about the operation of the Site or the services we provide from the site, including error reports or requests for enhancements.

• Log Information: Our servers automatically record and log basic information that your application sends. These server logs may include information such as your message, Internet Protocol address, other addressing information, the date and time of your request and an authentication token used to validate the identity of you and your computer.

## Age Limitation

This Site is not directed to persons under the age of 18. If you become aware that your child has provided us with personal information without your consent, please contact us at [support@squadlocker.com](mailto:support@squadlocker.com) or (888) 885-6253. We do not knowingly collect or solicit information from, market to or accept Service from persons under 18 years old. If we become aware that a person under 18 has provided us with personal information, we take steps to remove such information and terminate the person’s account.

## Why we need your personal information

The information we collect from what you tell us and what we gather automatically is used for one or more of the following general purposes:

• Customize the content you see

• If you are acting on behalf of a Group as authorized in the TOS, we may use information you provide to contact other members of the Group to obtain orders, and in that case other members of the Group may have access to contact and other information you provide

• If your information has been added to the Site as part of a Group, we may provide other members of the Group access to certain contact and other information you provide

• Conduct advertising and research

• Complete your purchases

• Contact you about your account

• Send you newsletters by mail or email about our Site

• Ask you for your feedback to help make our Site better

• Respond to your email requests for information and/or customer Site

We may also use the information defined in this Privacy Policy to: resolve disputes, collect fees, and troubleshoot problems; enforce our Terms of Service (“TOS”); customize, measure, and improve the Site, content and layout; compare information for accuracy, and verify your identity; provide other Sites for you as described when we collect the information. Additionally, we may use your information as described below.

• Registration Information

We ask for Registration Information in order to verify your identity and to enable your use of the Site. We use third party banking organizations and other providers of payment Sites to bill you, and in that case we will, therefore, provide this billing provider with the necessary billing data.

We do not sell your Registration Information to anyone

We do not send you newsletters or promotional mail or email if you tell us not to. However, we will use e-mail to send you messages about faults and Site issues. We may also use e-mail to keep you up to date with news about the Site.

• Order Information

We use your Order Information to complete and customize your orders, and may give this information to subcontractors in connection with order processing and fulfilment. In general, we will otherwise provide third parties access to your Order Information (except as specified by you). In addition, we may use and disclose it in aggregate form, for benchmarking, improvements to products and services, or marketing. If required by law, we reserve the right to pre-screen, review, flag, filter, modify, refuse or remove any or all Order Information.

• Reviews and Comments

We use Reviews and Comments for the purpose of providing content to other users of the site, and for improving our products and services. In addition, as noted in our TOS, we have the right to use, reproduce, modify, adapt, publish, perform, translate, create derivative works from, distribute, and display Reviews and Comments throughout the world in any media. However, if required by law, we reserve the right to pre-screen, review, flag, filter, modify, refuse or remove any or all Reviews and Comments from the Site.

• Log Information

We will use this routing information to provide you with access to the Site and for statistical information, for operating the Site and improving our products and services.

## Sharing your information with third parties

If the ownership of our business changes, either completely or substantially, we may transfer your information to the new owner so that the website may continue to operate. Furthermore, in certain situations described below, we will provide your personally identifying information to third parties:

• We may be required to disclose user information pursuant to lawful requests, such as subpoenas or court orders, or in compliance with applicable laws. Additionally, we may share account or other information when we believe it is necessary to comply with law, protect our interests or property, or prevent fraud or other illegal activity perpetrated through the website or using our name. This may include sharing information with other companies, lawyers, or government agencies.

• We may offer products or services jointly with other companies and individuals using the website. (Collectively, these may be referred to as the “Third-Party Providers.”) You understand and agree that if you use the website to connect with a Third-Party Provider, we may share your information with the applicable Third-Party Provider to facilitate your transaction.

• We share your personal information with the vendors (companies) that help us process transactions, such as charging your credit card when you make purchases. Any such sharing is always done subject to a legal agreement that requires them to keep your personal information strictly confidential.

## Account Security

The security of your account relies on your protection of your password. You are responsible for maintaining the security of your password. You are solely responsible for any and all activities that occur under your account. You may not share your password with anyone. We will never ask you to send your password or other sensitive information to us in an email, though we may ask you to enter this type of information on the Site. Any email or other communication requesting your password, asking you to provide sensitive account information via email, or linking to a website with a URL that does not begin with http://www.squadlocker.com should be treated as unauthorized and suspicious and should be reported to us immediately at [support@squadlocker.com](mailto:support@squadlocker.com). If you do share your password with a third party for any reason, the third party will have access to your account and your personal information, and you may be responsible for actions taken using your password. If you believe someone else has obtained access to your password, please change it immediately by logging in to your account at http://www.squadlocker.com and changing your Profile settings. If you believe that an unauthorized access has already occurred please report it immediately at [support@squadlocker.com](mailto:support@squadlocker.com). We may have access to your password and may use such password to access your account for debugging, quality assurance, or other internal purposes.

## Data Security

We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. While we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your personal information, no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure and we cannot guarantee its absolute security. In the event of an inadvertent disclosure of your personal information we will take all commercially reasonable steps to limit and remedy the disclosure as required by the applicable law. If you have any questions about security regarding out Service, you can contact us via email or telephone at [support@squadlocker.com](mailto:support@squadlocker.com) (888) 885-6253.

## How long personal information is kept

We will retain your information for as long as is necessary to: (1) provide the use of the Site; (2) invoice to you your use of the Site and to maintain records until invoicing for the Site cannot be lawfully challenged and legal proceedings may no longer be pursued; (3) communicate with you regarding other products and services that we offer; (4) comply with applicable legislation, regulatory requests and relevant orders from competent courts; (5) enforce our TOS; or (6) fulfill any of the other purposes detailed in this Privacy Policy.

## Changing or removing information

You can review and modify most of your personal information at any time by accessing your account.  Also, upon your request, we will use commercially reasonable efforts to functionally remove you and your personal information from the website.  Removed information may persist in backup or archived copies, but will not be generally available to users of the website and or other third parties.

## Cookies

Cookies are files that your Web browser puts on your computer when you visit a website. We use cookies to tell us how often you visit our website, and what pages you go to on our website. Sometimes we use files from other companies (called third-party cookies) to help us see where people go on our website, to improve our Sites and the performance of our advertising. Unless you give us permission, the cookies we use do not store any personally identifying information. For example, If you choose the option to “remember my email address” on our login page, we will store the information we need to identify you on your next visit in a cookie on your computer.

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and Sites of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies

## Links to other sites

The Site may contain links to third party web sites and may redirect you to third party web sites (“Third Party Sites”). These Third Party Sites may include, among others, service providers who have a relationship with us. Third Party Sites are not under our control, and we are not responsible for such Third Party Sites, including without limitation the accuracy, sufficiency, correctness, reliability, veracity, completeness, or timeliness thereof, any link contained therein, or any changes or updates thereto. The inclusion or access to Third Party Sites does not imply an endorsement thereof by us or of the provider of such content or service, or of any third party web site. We reserve the right to terminate any link or linking program at any time. Please be aware that when you enter a Third Party Site, any information you provide, including financial information, is subject to the terms of use and privacy policy of that Third Party Site.

## Can this privacy policy be modified?

We reserve the right to modify the provisions of this Privacy Policy if we deem it necessary.  Each time you use the Service, the current version of the Privacy Policy will apply. Accordingly, when you use the Service, you should check the date of this Privacy Policy (which appears at the top of the Privacy Policy) and review any changes since the last version. Our business changes frequently and this Privacy Policy is subject to change from time to time. You are encouraged to check the Site regularly for any changes to this Privacy Policy. Unless stated otherwise, our current Privacy Policy applies to all information that we have about you.

## Governing Law

This Privacy Policy is governed by the laws of Rhode Island, U.S.A. without giving effect to any principles of conflict of law.

## Your California Privacy Rights

California Civil Code Section 1798.83 permits customers who are California residents and who have provided the Company with “personal information” (as that term is defined in Section 1798.83) to request certain information about the disclosure of that information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes. If you are a California resident with questions regarding this, please contact us at [support@squadlocker.com](mailto:support@squadlocker.com) or (888) 885-6253 or at Squadlocker, Inc., attn.: PRIVACY, 240 Bald Hill Road, Warwick, RI 02886-1126.

## Contact Us

To contact us with your questions or comments regarding this Privacy Policy or the information collection and dissemination practices of the Service, please email us at [support@squadlocker.com](mailto:support@squadlocker.com). To see the Terms of Service that apply to the Service, see www.squadlocker.com/terms.  All trademarks, service marks, and other proprietary materials herein are the property of Squadlocker.
